var questions = [
    {
        question:"7 * 6",
        choices:[89,40,42,48],
        answer:42
    },
    {
        question:"4 * 6",
        choices:[16,24,20,22],
        answer:24
    },
    {
        question:"9 * 6",
        choices:[54,50,76,22],
        answer:54
    },
    {
        question:"10 * 8",
        choices:[10,8,9,80],
        answer:80
    },
    {
        question:"8 * 4",
        choices:[8,4,32,12],
        answer:32
    },
    {
        question:"10 * 9",
        choices:[19,90,10,9],
        answer:90
    },
    {
        question:"6 * 6",
        choices:[36,41,45,30],
        answer:36
    },
    {
        question:"2 * 9",
        choices:[10,19,11,18],
        answer:18
    },
    {
        question:"2 * 3",
        choices:[5,6,60,15],
        answer:6
    }, 
    {
        question:"5 * 1",
        choices:[51,15,5,6],
        answer:5
    },
    {
        question:"9 * 9",
        choices:[21,18,31,81],
        answer:81
    },
    {
        question:"4 * 4",
        choices:[16,8,21,18],
        answer:16
    },
    {
        question:"7 * 9",
        choices:[24,64,63,79],
        answer:63
    },
    {
        question:"5 * 7",
        choices:[25,30,35,45],
        answer:35
    },
    {
        question:"5 * 5",
        choices:[21,19,35,25],
        answer:25
    },
    {
        question:"3 * 6",
        choices:[18,16,15,19],
        answer:18
    },
    {
        question:"10 * 7",
        choices:[12,18,70,60],
        answer:70
    },
    {
        question:"4 * 3",
        choices:[10,12,21,31],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"8 * 9",
        choices:[17,21,18,72],
        answer:3
    }, 
    {
        question:"10 * 6",
        choices:[10,60,16,12],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"9 * 8",
        choices:[72,70,58,54],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"5 * 6",
        choices:[11,10,30,20],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"9 * 10",
        choices:[18,19,21,90],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"6 * 4",
        choices:[32,36,24,27],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"2 * 6",
        choices:[8,12,18,31],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"1 * 9",
        choices:[9,1,10,12],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"9 * 9",
        choices:[72,21,18,81],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"6 * 9",
        choices:[34,54,81,90],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"6 * 5",
        choices:[9,25,35,45],
        answer:2
    }, 
    {
        question:"2 * 5",
        choices:[11,21,11,10],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"9 * 4",
        choices:[36,35,90,27],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"4 * 8",
        choices:[31,30,32,72],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"8 * 6",
        choices:[29,36,54,48],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"4 * 1",
        choices:[14,4,41,5],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"7 * 7",
        choices:[35,14,21,49],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"2 * 10",
        choices:[21,20,12,30],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"8 * 5",
        choices:[40,35,89,100],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"6 * 8",
        choices:[43,,,48],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"2 * 8",
        choices:[2,4,16,24],
        answer:2
    }, 
    {
        question:"4 * 10",
        choices:[14,40,10,4],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"9 * 1",
        choices:[91,19,10,9],
        answer:4
    },
    {
        question:"10 * 10",
        choices:[100,1,10,20],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"7 * 10",
        choices:[7,70,10,17],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"5 * 8",
        choices:[5,8,40,35],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"8 * 10",
        choices:[8,80,10,18],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"3 * 9",
        choices:[25,45,21,27],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"3 * 1",
        choices:[,,,3],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"3 * 7",
        choices:[3,73,21,7],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"3 * 10",
        choices:[30,3,13,20],
        answer:0
    }, 
    {
        question:"6 * 7",
        choices:[54,48,36,42],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"3 * 5",
        choices:[3,5,15,8],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"1 * 6",
        choices:[2,1,6,61],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"1 * 10",
        choices:[21,10,11,1],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"2 * 7",
        choices:[21,2,7,14],
        answer:3
    }, 
    {
        question:"1 * 5",
        choices:[5,1,15,51],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"9 * 7",
        choices:[8,63,9,7],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"2 * 1",
        choices:[1,21,2,12],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"4 * 2",
        choices:[8,6,10,1],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"1 * 7",
        choices:[1,17,15,7],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"1 * 8",
        choices:[18,1,8,9],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"9 * 5",
        choices:[12,40,55,45],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"6 * 3",
        choices:[36,9,18,15],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"2 * 8",
        choices:[10,14,12,16],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"7 * 5",
        choices:[,,,35],
        answer:3
    }, 
    {
        question:"2 * 2",
        choices:[4,12,22,11],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"5 * 9",
        choices:[45,40,35,18],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"9 * 2",
        choices:[10,11,18,9],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"7 * 2",
        choices:[10,9,11,14],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"7 * 3",
        choices:[11,3,7,21],
        answer:3
    }, 
    {
        question:"4 * 7",
        choices:[4,28,20,7],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"8 * 2",
        choices:[16,17,8,2],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"8 * 1",
        choices:[11,80,8,1],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"6 * 1",
        choices:[9,6,12,11],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"10 * 1",
        choices:[1,2,11,10],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:" * 1",
        choices:[11,21,1,2],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"5 * 3",
        choices:[11,10,18,15],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"5 * 4",
        choices:[20,21,13,15],
        answer:0
    }, 
    {
        question:"8 * 7",
        choices:[91,12,56,18],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"10 * 3",
        choices:[10,30,3,21],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"5 * 2",
        choices:[2,5,7,10],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"6 * 2",
        choices:[12,11,10,8],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"1 * 2",
        choices:[3,12,2,1],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"10 * 5",
        choices:[11,10,50,43],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"3 * 2",
        choices:[8,6,5,4],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"3 * 3",
        choices:[33,30,3,9],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"1 * 3",
        choices:[9,3,1,32],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"10 * 2",
        choices:[20,21,30,10],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"7 * 1",
        choices:[6,3,7,8],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"3 * 4",
        choices:[11,12,14,13],
        answer:1
    }, 
    {
        question:"10 * 4",
        choices:[10,32,12,40],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"4 * 9",
        choices:[72,36,35,89],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"5 * 10",
        choices:[56,23,50,22],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"8 * 3",
        choices:[23,24,22,21],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"7 * 4",
        choices:[27,24,23,28],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"9 * 3",
        choices:[23,25,27,24],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"8 * 8",
        choices:[48,51,65,64],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"1 * 4",
        choices:[0,4,1,6],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"6 * 10",
        choices:[70,60,06,10],
        answer:1
    }, 
    {
        question:"7 * 8",
        choices:[62,48,54,56],
        answer:3
    }
]




























































